[
  {
    "Answer4": "Slapping",
    "Answer3": "Octaves",
    "Answer2": "Tapping",
    "Score": "3",
    "Answer1": "Shredding",
    "File_Location": "Flatwound-2-Full.mp3",
    "Question": "The bass line in this track is employing which technique?",
    "Track_Length": "21",
    "Created": "IfAtQ-QVoNKt^4fquAf!nKY)^i.irQGFEalJFQEQJKavSJG%F",
    "Level": "2",
    "File_Path": "Flatwound-2-Full.mp3",
    "Correct_Answer": "Octaves",
    "Hint": "This technique utilizes playing the same note one adjacent strings and can be heard on countless disco records.",
    "ID": "mk-74849585",
    "Type": "music-knowledge",
    "Active": "true"
  },
  {
    "Answer4": "Calypso",
    "Answer3": "Motown",
    "Answer2": "World Music",
    "Score": "3",
    "Answer1": "Classical",
    "File_Location": "MotownDrumBeat.mp3",
    "Question": "This style of drum groove is likely to be found in which musical genre?",
    "Track_Length": "21",
    "Created": "IfAtQ-QVoNKt^4fquAf!nKY)^i.irQGFEalJFQEQJKavSJG%F",
    "Level": "2",
    "File_Path": "MotownDrumBeat.mp3",
    "Correct_Answer": "Motown",
    "Hint": "This style of drumbeat can be heard on countless recordings beginning in the 1960's. Drummers like Bennie Benjamin, Uriel Jones, and Pistol Allen perfected the beat that created some of the greatest songs of all time.",
    "ID": "mk-74849585",
    "Type": "music-knowledge",
    "Active": "true"
  },
  {
    "Answer4": "Flatwound",
    "Answer3": "Roundwound",
    "Answer2": "Tapewound",
    "Score": "3",
    "Answer1": "Stringwound",
    "File_Location": "Flatwound.mp3",
    "Question": "Which type of string winding is most likely being used on this bass groove",
    "Track_Length": "21",
    "Created": "IfAtQ-QVoNKt^4fquAf!nKY)^i.irQGFEalJFQEQJKavSJG%F",
    "Level": "2",
    "File_Path": "Flatwound.mp3",
    "Correct_Answer": "Flatwound",
    "Hint": "These strings were the first type of strings used on electric bass and are more gentle on the fingers thanksto their flat windings.",
    "ID": "mk-98283783",
    "Type": "music-knowledge",
    "Active": "true"
  },
  {
    "Answer4": "Miramba",
    "Answer3": "Metronome",
    "Answer2": "Pulse",
    "Score": "1",
    "Answer1": "Violin",
    "File_Location": "Metronome.mp3",
    "Question": "This device is used by musicians to help keep a consistent tempo.",
    "Track_Length": "22",
    "Created": "IfAtQ-QVoNKt^4fquAf!nKY)^i.irQGFEalJFQEQJKavSJG%F",
    "Level": "1",
    "File_Path": "Metronome.mp3",
    "Correct_Answer": "Metronome",
    "Hint": "Used by musicians for centruies, this device works by providing a steady pulse which allows a musician to play along in time.",
    "ID": "mm3939349",
    "Type": "music-knowledge",
    "Active": "true"
  },
  {
    "Answer4": "Click Track",
    "Answer3": "Rhythm Track",
    "Answer2": "Rim Shot",
    "Score": "1",
    "Answer1": "Chase Fade",
    "File_Location": "Click-Track.mp3",
    "Question": "This type of track is used to help keep musicians in time when recording or performing.",
    "Track_Length": "22",
    "Created": "IfAtQ-QVoNKt^4fquAf!nKY)^i.irQGFEalJFQEQJKavSJG%F",
    "Level": "1",
    "File_Path": "Click-Track.mp3",
    "Correct_Answer": "Click Track",
    "Hint": "Similar to a metronome, this tool is used when it's necessary for musicians to stay in time or when performing live and playing along with pre-recorded audio.",
    "ID": "mm0304-3-40049",
    "Type": "music-knowledge",
    "Active": "true"
  },
  {
    "Answer4": "Octave",
    "Answer2": "Scale",
    "Answer3": "Harmony",
    "File_Path": "5000135.mp3",
    "Answer1": "Chord",
    "Hint": "A set of musical notes ordered by fundamental frequency or pitch.",
    "File_Location": "mjr_blues_scale_pno.mp3",
    "Created": "IfAtQ-QVoNKt^4fquAf!nKY)^i.igWZMV",
    "Score": "4",
    "Type": "music-knowledge",
    "Correct_Answer": "Scale",
    "Track_Length": "25",
    "Question": "This musical excerpt is an example of which of the following?",
    "Level": "1",
    "ID": "5000135"
  },
  {
    "Answer4": "Tom Tom",
    "Answer2": "Snare Drum",
    "Answer3": "Floor Tom",
    "File_Path": "900000.mp3",
    "Answer1": "Bass Drum",
    "Hint": "This instrument produces a low booming sound that along with a snare drum forms the foundation of a drum kit.",
    "File_Location": "Bass_Drum.mp3",
    "Created": "IfAtQ-QVoNKt^4fquAf!nKY)^i.i!ZFFatGDL",
    "Score": "2",
    "Type": "music-knowledge",
    "Correct_Answer": "Bass Drum",
    "Track_Length": "25",
    "Question": "What is the name of the drum featured in this clip?",
    "Level": "1",
    "ID": "900000"
  },
  {
    "Answer4": "Select Answer 4",
    "Answer4_File_Path": "mq-drum-bass-4.mp3",
    "Answer4_Track_Length": "24",
    "Answer2": "Select Answer 2",
    "Answer2_File_Path": "mq-drum-bass-2.mp3",
    "Answer2_Track_Length": "24",
    "Answer3": "Select Answer 3",
    "Answer3_File_Path": "mq-drum-bass-3.mp3",
    "Answer3_Track_Length": "24",
    "File_Path": "mq-drum-bass-1.mp3",
    "Answer1": "Select Answer 1",
    "Answer1_File_Path": "mq-drum-bass-1.mp3",
    "Answer1_Track_Length": "24",
    "Hint": "Listen closely to what the hi-hat is playing.",
    "File_Location": "mq-drum-bass-1.mp3",
    "Created": "IfAtQ-QVoNKt^4fquAf!nKY)^i.i!ZFFatGDL",
    "Score": "2",
    "Type": "music-memory",
    "Correct_Answer": "Select Answer 1",
    "Track_Length": "24",
    "Question": "Listen carefully to this track, then click the play button next to each of the potential answers, then select the answer that's identical to what you first heard.",
    "Level": "1",
    "ID": "mm10000"
  },
  {
    "Answer4": "Big Muff Pi",
    "Answer3": "Ibanez Tube Screamer",
    "Answer2": "Pro Co RAT",
    "Score": "1",
    "Answer1": "Boss SD-1 Super Overdrive",
    "File_Location": "TubeScreamer.mp3",
    "Question": "What's the name of the little green stomp box used in this clip?",
    "Track_Length": "15",
    "Created": "IfAtQ-QVoNKt^4fquAf!nKY)^i.irQGFEalJFQEQJKavSJG%F",
    "Level": "1",
    "File_Path": "TubeScreamer.mp3",
    "Correct_Answer": "Ibanez Tube Screamer",
    "Hint": "This legendary stompbox is one of the most popular overdrive pedals and is best known for its ability to help drive a tube amplifier.The original TS808 was first released in the late 1970s and is characterized by its mid-boost.",
    "ID": "8393847584939",
    "Type": "music-knowledge",
    "Active": "true"
  },
  {
    "Answer4": "Digital Delay",
    "Answer3": "Spring Reverb",
    "Answer2": "Phase Shifting",
    "Score": "1",
    "Answer1": "Flanging",
    "File_Location": "Flanger.mp3",
    "Question": "What is the name of this modulation effect?",
    "Track_Length": "24",
    "Created": "IfAtQ-QVoNKt^4fquAf!nKY)^i.irQGFEalJFQEQJKavSJG%F",
    "Level": "1",
    "File_Path": "Flanger.mp3",
    "Correct_Answer": "Flanging",
    "Hint": "This modulation effect is produced by mixing two signals together, where one has a slight delay.",
    "ID": "mk39384849",
    "Type": "music-knowledge",
    "Active": "true"
  },
  {
    "Answer4": "Select Answer 4",
    "Answer4_File_Path": "mq2-drum-bass-4.mp3",
    "Answer4_Track_Length": "24",
    "Answer2": "Select Answer 2",
    "Answer2_File_Path": "mq2-drum-bass-2.mp3",
    "Answer2_Track_Length": "24",
    "Answer3": "Select Answer 3",
    "Answer3_File_Path": "mq2-drum-bass-3.mp3",
    "Answer3_Track_Length": "24",
    "File_Path": "mq2-drum-bass-4.mp3",
    "Answer1": "Select Answer 1",
    "Answer1_File_Path": "mq2-drum-bass-1.mp3",
    "Answer1_Track_Length": "24",
    "Hint": "The original track was pretty funky.",
    "File_Location": "mq2-drum-bass-4.mp3",
    "Created": "IfAtQ-QVoNKt^4fquAf!nKY)^i.i!ZFFatGDL",
    "Score": "2",
    "Type": "music-memory",
    "Correct_Answer": "Select Answer 4",
    "Track_Length": "21",
    "Question": "Listen carefully to this track, then click the play button next to each of the potential answers, then select the answer that's identical to what you first heard.",
    "Level": "1",
    "ID": "mm10000"
  }
]
